Guide to the Central Washington University Facilities Management Department, Planning and Construction Files 1954-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Facilities Management Department, Planning and Construction Files
1954-2000
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG006-05-71
Central Washington University. Facilities Management Department
10.75 cubic feet 22 boxes Minutes, reports, and photographs in good condition
This collection documents the construction and remodeling to the buildings and grounds of Central Washington University. Ellensburg, WA, 1954-2000.
Historical Note
Central Washington University's Facilities Management Department was initially established under the supervision of the Washington State Normal School Board of Trustees when the school opened in 1891. In 1910, a Supervisor of Buildings and Grounds was appointed and given the responsibility for facilities management of the campus. During the 1920s, a Business Manager replaced the Supervisor of Buildings and Grounds consolidating departments. The Facilities Management Department was reorganized in 1986 and included the planning division.
This collection represents growth at Central Washington University, 1954-2000. The included Campus Site and Development Committee minutes and correspondence outline the planning of Central's Facilities Management Department. This collection also includes photographs and drawings that document additions and modifications to buildings and landscaping on campus.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Organized into four series: I. Campus Site and Development Committee; II. Technical Data Collection; III. Photographs; IV. Oversized materials
Open to the public for educational research.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University. Facilities Management Department
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Universities & colleges--United States; College buildings
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- Campus Site and Development Committee, 1961-2000; I
  This series contains planning documents of the Campus Site and Development Committee. The files of the committee's meeting minutes also include as attachments documents which were discussed at the meetings. These include planning documents for buildings, facilities, grounds, and any changes to the campus. Another group of files are the correspondence files for the committee. These files include letters concerning membership to the committee as well as letters concerning the campus facilities.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-7)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-8)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-10)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-11)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-12)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-13)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-14)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-15)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-16)
  - Minutes, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1-17)
  - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-9)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-10)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-11)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-12)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-13)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-14)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-15)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-16)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-17)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-18)
  - Minutes, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 2-19)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 3-6)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 3-7)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 3-8)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 3-9)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 3-10)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 3-11)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 3-12)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 3-13)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 3-14)
  - Revised schematic studies – physical plant facilities, June 18, 1969 (Box-folder 3-15)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 3-16)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 3-17)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 3-18)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 3-19)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 3-20)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-3)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-6)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-7)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-8)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-9)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-10)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-11)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-12)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-13)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-14)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-15)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-16)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 4-17)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 4-18)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 4-19)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 4-20)
- Technical Data Collection Files, 1954-1990; II
  This series contains the technical files of the facilities department. Included are planning documents, drawings and reports. This includes planning documents for new buildings and the remodeling of old buildings. Also included are energy audits and other technical reports. Also present are files of the utilities on campus. These files are arranged by the Technical Data (TD) Collection number which was assigned by the facilities department.
  These files are arranged by the Technical Data (TD) Collection number, which was assigned by the Facilities Management Department.
  - Report on Survey for Deferred Maintenance, June 1, 1954; TD 0301 (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Report on Survey for deferred maintenance, June 1, 1954; TD 0301 (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Feasibility study for a central food storage facility, September 2, 1971; TD 0312 (Box-folder 5-3)
  - A comparison of cafeteria serving facilities: multiple line and scramble systems, TD 0313 (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Systems studies for the student village, phase II, June 20, 1969; TD 0314 (Box-folder 5-5)
  - Science Building, 1966; TD 0318 (Box-folder 5-6)
  - North campus urban renewal department, March 6, 1968; TD 0319 (Box-folder 5-7)
  - Building plans and information, 1968; TD 0320 (Box-folder 5-8)
  - Construction comparison study for Brooklane village married student housing, August 15, 1969; TD 0330 (Box-folder 5-9)
  - An economic analysis of comparative energy costs for CWSC, December 30, 1971; TD 0334 (Box-folder 5-10)
  - Mann Plan – General Development Plan, February 10, 1969; TD 0341 (Box-folder 5-11)
  - Utility distribution systems study, February 14, 1969; TD 0345 (Box-folder 5-12)
  - Report of survey. Heating utility requirements for new campus buildings, May 14, 1966; TD 0347 (Box-folder 6-1)
  - Landscape Master Plan, May 25, 1970; TD 0348 (Box-folder 6-2)
  - Preliminary corrosion survey. A proposal, April 9, 1971; TD 353 (Box-folder 6-3)
  - Design development. Remodel Boiler Plan, September 28, 1971; TD 0382 (Box-folder 6-4)
  - Supplementary report to a study and report on steam generation and boiler loading, May 16, 1972; TD 0414 (Box-folder 6-5)
  - Report of Study. Electrical service and distribution systems, May 15, 1972; TD 0415 (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Utility Study. Water System-Report Draft, April 6, 1972; TD 0425 (Box-folder 6-7)
  - Report of Study. Steam Generation and boiler loading, March 30, 1972; TD 0427 (Box-folder 6-8)
  - Report of Study. Steam Generation and boiler loading, March 30, 1972; TD 0427 (Box-folder 6-9)
  - Balancing Report of Chilled Water and Air Systems, June 25, 1971; TD 0430 (Box-folder 6-10)
  - Revised schematic studies. Physical plant facilities, June 18, 1969; TD 0431 (Box-folder 6-11)
  - Report of study. Electric service and distribution systems, May 15, 1972; TD 0432 (Box-folder 6-12)
  - Report of study. Extension and expansion campus utilities, 1971-1973; TD 0456 (Box-folder 6-13)
  - Schematic Submittal. Emergency Generator System, December 8, 1972; TD 0491 (Box-folder 6-14)
  - Schematic Studies for Physical Plant Facilities, June 26, 1968; TD 0492 (Box-folder 6-15)
  - Report of study. Steam Generation and boiler loading, March 30, 1972; TD 0495 (Box-folder 6-16)
  - Report of Sruvey Heating Utility Requirements for New Campus Buildings, March 14, 1966; TD 0496 (Box-folder 7-1)
  - Comprehensive Utility Study for CWSC, 1972; TD 0497 (Box-folder 7-2)
  - Campus Energy supply study, 1972; TD 0498 (Box-folder 7-3)
  - Design Development Documents for Physical Plant Facilities, 1969; TD 0499 (Box-folder 7-4)
  - Extension and Expansion Campus Utilities, 1971-1973; TD 0500 (Box-folder 7-5)
  - Report of Study. Steam Generation and Boiler loading, March 30, 1972; TD 0501 (Box-folder 7-6)
  - Report of Study. Electrical Service and Distribution Systems, May 15, 1972; TD 0502 (Box-folder 7-7)
  - Foundation Investigation. Library Instruction Complex, July, 1971; TD 0504 (Box-folder 7-8)
  - Steam Generation and Boiler Loading, 1973; TD 0517 (Box-folder 7-9)
  - Report. The use of Aerial photography to detect steam lines at CWSC, July 15, 1970; TD 0576 (Box-folder 7-10)
  - Proposal. Mapping and Monumentation, 1967; TD 0577 (Box-folder 7-11)
  - Campus Building Plans and Information, 1973; TD 0586 (Box-folder 7-12)
  - CWSC. General Development Plan, 1969; TD 0590 (Box-folder 7-13)
  - Space analysis. Administration Bldg. Mitchell Hall, 1964; TD 0673 (Box-folder 7-14)
  - Study-Administration Bldg., TD 0674 (Box-folder 7-15)
  - Administration Building. Design Development Phase, 1964; TD 0675 (Box-folder 7-16)
  - Foundation Investigation Student Village, July 7, 1967; TD 0783 (Box-folder 8-1)
  - Dormitory landscape program, 1966; TD 0790 (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Auxiliary Services Buildings. Floor Plans and Information, 1967; TD 0804 (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Auxiliary Services Buildings, September, 1971; TD 0806 (Box-folder 8-4)
  - Auxiliary Services Buildings, August, 1982; TD 0806 (Box-folder 8-5)
  - Building Plans and Information, 1968; TD 0807 (Box-folder 8-6)
  - Energy recovery from solid waste by pyrolysis for Kittitas County, July, 1972; TD 0808 (Box-folder 8-7)
  - Report of Survey Heating Utility Requirements for New Campus Buildings, 1966; TD 0811 (Box-folder 8-8)
  - Systems Studies for the Student Village, Phase II, 1969; TD 0815 (Box-folder 8-9)
  - Recommendations for a pesticide storage facility, January 18, 1974; TD 0830 (Box-folder 8-10)
  - Report of Student. Central Chilled Water System vs. Separate Refrigeration Plants for Campus Buildings, 1967; TD 0834 (Box-folder 8-11)
  - Feasibility Study. Utilities – Mechanical. Well and Water System, 1973; TD 0838 (Box-folder 8-12)
  - Report of a preliminary survey of the steam boiler plan and distribution system relative to present efficiency and future utilization in the expansion program, May, 1958; TD 0850 (Box-folder 8-13)
  - Emergency Generator System. Boiler Plant, February 9, 1973; TD 0855 (Box-folder 8-14)
  - Cathodic Protection. Corrosion Control Survey. Buried Utilities., TD 0856 (Box-folder 8-15)
  - Report of Study. Electrical Service and Distribution Systems, May 15, 1972; TD 0857 (Box-folder 8-16)
  - Balancing Report of Chilled Water and Air Systems, 1971; TD 0874 (Box-folder 8-17)
  - A Comparative Study of Centralized vs. Unit Kitchen Food Service Facilities, 1964; TD 0888 (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Report for Electrical Distribution requirements for new campus buildings, 1966; TD 0891 (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Program requirements. Remodeling and addition to Samuelson College Union, 1964; TD 0892 (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Space requirements for the Samuelson College Union Building, 1966; TD 0893 (Box-folder 9-4)
  - Groundwater study. Student union Building, 1968; TD 0894 (Box-folder 9-5)
  - Operation Check, Year book, 1966; TD 0895 (Box-folder 9-6)
  - Test Report. Norton Corrosion Engineers, 1968; TD 0896 (Box-folder 9-7)
  - Operational Check Report. Underground Steam and Water Lines, 1971; TD 0898 (Box-folder 9-8)
  - Conversion of Existing Library Building into Classrooms, TD 0899 (Box-folder 9-9)
  - Report on Institute on Cluster Colleges, 1970; TD 0900-TD 0901 (Box-folder 9-10)
  - Proposal for a classroom building for the student village, 1970; TD 0902 (Box-folder 9-11)
  - Report of Survey of Future Utility Requirements, 1964; TD 0907 (Box-folder 9-12)
  - Comparison of Fuel Cost for Residential Space Heating, 1965; TD 0909 (Box-folder 9-13)
  - Report of Survey of Future utility requirements, 1964; TD 0931 (Box-folder 9-14)
  - Survey and report. Underground steam distribution system and central heating plant, January, 1960; TD 0932 (Box-folder 9-15)
  - Report of a preliminary survey of the steam boiler plant, and distribution system relative to present efficiency and future utilization in the expansion program, May, 1958; TD 0933 (Box-folder 9-16)
  - Utilities Study for CWSC, 1973; TD 0934 (Box-folder 9-17)
  - Utility Distribution Systems Study, February 14, 1969; TD 0942 (Box-folder 9-18)
  - Utilities Study for CWSC, 1972; TD 0964 (Box-folder 9-19)
  - Report of Study. Steam Generation and Boiler Loading, 1972; TD 0965 (Box-folder 9-20)
  - Campus-wide sewer analysis, July 16, 1974; TD 0973 (Box-folder 9-21)
  - Landscape master plan for CWSC, May 25, 1970; TD 0976 (Box-folder 9-22)
  - Foundation Investigation. Fine and applied arts building, 1966; TD 1013 (Box-folder 9-23)
  - Foundation Investigation. Technology and Industrial Education Building, 1968; TD 1019 (Box-folder 9-24)
  - Foundation Investigation. Language and Literature Building, 1969; TD 1020 (Box-folder 9-25)
  - Foundation Investigation. New Administration Building, 1966; TD 1021 (Box-folder 9-26)
  - Feasibility Study: Physical Plant facility, April 16, 1968; TD 1022 (Box-folder 9-27)
  - Design Development Documents for Physical Plant Facilities, 1967; TD 1023 (Box-folder 9-28)
  - Physical Education. Preliminary Report, June, 1957; TD 1024 (Box-folder 9-29)
  - Foundation Investigation. Psychology Building, 1970; TD 1026 (Box-folder 9-30)
  - Building Program and Budget, 1969; TD 1028 (Box-folder 10-1)
  - Corrosion Control Survey, 1973; TD 1031 (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Fuel Conservation Curves, 1975; TD 1052 (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Water-use statistics, 1975; TD 1095 (Box-folder 10-4)
  - CWSC Campus Floor Plans, circa 1962; TD 1120 (Box-folder 10-5)
  - Energy Recovery from Solid Waste by Pyrolysis for Kittitas County, 1972; TD 1126 (Box-folder 10-6)
  - Technical Proposal for Utility Extension. Surpervisory Control Expansion, 1975; TD 1129 (Box-folder 10-7)
  - Old Heating Plant Gas Consumption, 1965-1967; TD 1132 (Box-folder 10-8)
  - Photos of Duct repair, 1975; TD 1159 (Box-folder 10-9)
  - Mechanical construction photos, 1975; TD 1160 (Box-folder 10-10)
  - Log of photos for corroded steam line project, 1975; TD 1161 (Box-folder 10-11)
  - Floor record photos, 1974; TD 1163 (Box-folder 10-12)
  - Barge Hall Quadrangle Design Proposal, 1969; TD 1164 (Box-folder 10-13)
  - Photos for Boiler/Chiller loop project, 1975; TD 1175 (Box-folder 10-14)
  - Survey and classification of Academic buildings HVAC Systems, 1976; TD 1183 (Box-folder 10-15)
  - Safety Inspection Recommendations, 1974; TD 1184 (Box-folder 10-16)
  - Solid Waste Transfer building design notes, 1975; TD 1185 (Box-folder 10-17)
  - Photographs. New Boiler House, 1974; TD 1260 (Box-folder 11-1)
  - Photos, Ground’s Building Spray Booth Modification, 1975; TD 1275 (Box-folder 11-2)
  - Indexes for Construction. Capital Projects (Completed), 1948-1974; TD 1277A (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Indexes for Construction. Capital Projects (Completed), 1948-1974; TD 1277A (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Indexes for Construction. Capital Projects (Completed), 1948-1974; TD 1277A (Box-folder 11-5)
  - Indexes for Construction. Capital Projects (Completed), 1948-1974; TD 1277A (Box-folder 11-6)
  - Barge Hall restoration standards for maintenance and operation, 1977; TD 1315 (Box-folder 11-7)
  - Standards for new construction, 1968; TD 1317 (Box-folder 11-8)
  - Space requirements to be provided in the Bouillon Hall Project, 1977; TD 1327 (Box-folder 11-9)
  - Heat recovery methods considered for the CWSC Psychology Building, 1977; TD 1328 (Box-folder 11-10)
  - Space requirements to be provided in the Barge Hall Restoration Project, 1977; TD 1329 (Box-folder 11-11)
  - Space requirements to be provided in the McConnell Hall Project, TD 1330 (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Hazardous Agricultural Chemical Storage, 1976; TD 1331 (Box-folder 11-13)
  - Heating System Control Data, 1977; TD 1338 (Box-folder 11-14)
  - Energy conservation, 1977; TD 1348 (Box-folder 11-15)
  - Evaluation of Water Well, 1972; TD 1349 (Box-folder 11-16)
  - Water use plan, Summer 1977; TD 1350 (Box-folder 12-1)
  - Life Cycle Cost Analysis. Additions and alterations to McConnell Hall, 1977; TD 1366 (Box-folder 12-2)
  - Corrosion Protection Systems, 1977; TD 1371 (Box-folder 12-3)
  - Internal Water Treatment for Boilers and Connecting Systems, TD 1374 (Box-folder 12-4)
  - Administration Budget. Academic Billings, 1965; TD 1384 (Box-folder 12-5)
  - Energy conservation executive order, TD 1412 (Box-folder 12-6)
  - Cathodic Protection History, 1950-1973; TD 1419 (Box-folder 12-7)
  - Brooklane Village Construction Pre-planning, 1968-1970; TD 1423 (Box-folder 12-8)
  - Sewer Infiltration Program, 1971-1973; TD 1428 (Box-folder 12-9)
  - Traffic studies correspondence, 1964-1971; TD 1429 (Box-folder 12-10)
  - Cable Failure. Case history, 1970; TD 1431 (Box-folder 12-11)
  - Boiler plant expansion, 1972; TD 1433 (Box-folder 12-12)
  - College Heating planning, 1961; TD 1435 (Box-folder 12-13)
  - Study Proposal: Heating/Chiller plant, 1971; TD 1436 (Box-folder 12-14)
  - Construction permits, 1972-1973; TD 1438 (Box-folder 12-15)
  - Report power outage, 1972; TD 1440 (Box-folder 12-16)
  - Area lighting correspondence, 1959-1973; TD 1442 (Box-folder 12-17)
  - Property ownership physical plant, 1971; TD 1443 (Box-folder 12-18)
  - Storm sewer correspondence, 1970-1972; TD 1447 (Box-folder 12-19)
  - Railroad: Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific RR, 1967-1971; TD 1449 (Box-folder 12-20)
  - King Video (TV), 1966-1973; TD 1455 (Box-folder 12-21)
  - Historical Clock and bell systems, 1959-1972; TD 1457 (Box-folder 12-22)
  - CWSC/Ellensburg Telephone Co. Communications Duct-Sharing Correspondence, 1969-1972; TD 1458 (Box-folder 12-23)
  - CWU Site Land Acquisition, 1969-1973; TD 1461 (Box-folder 12-24)
  - CWU Land Ownership Adjacent North Boundary, 1971; TD 1466 (Box-folder 12-25)
  - Building Names, 1965-1969; TD 1467 (Box-folder 12-26)
  - Qualifications and Experience for Professional Engineering Services, 1975; TD 1479 (Box-folder 12-27)
  - Cathodic protection systems, 1966; TD 1510 (Box-folder 13-1)
  - Structural engineering report, Edison Hall, 1964; TD 1512 (Box-folder 13-2)
  - Annual physical facilities report, 1977; TD 1556 (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Summary of Ellensburg C.Y. Degree Days, 1978; TD 1567 (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Report on Air and Water Balancing, 1978; TD 1568 (Box-folder 13-5)
  - Annual operational inspection. Cathodic protection systems, 1978; TD 1599 (Box-folder 13-6)
  - Report on Freeze Damage, 1979; TD 1615 (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Testing and Balancing Report (HVAC) Submittal, 1978; TD 1618 (Box-folder 13-8)
  - Annual physical facilities report, 1979; TD 1643 (Box-folder 13-9)
  - Preliminary Energy audit survey form, 1979; TD 1644 (Box-folder 13-10)
  - Bouillon remodeling program, 1974; TD 1675 (Box-folder 13-11)
  - Polaroid pictures of campus buildings, 1980; TD 1679 (Box-folder 13-12)
  - Polaroid pictures of campus buildings, 1980; TD 1679 (Box-folder 13-13)
  - Backflow prevention – Cross connection campus resurvey (1 of 2), 1978; TD 1687 (Box-folder 13-14)
  - Backflow prevention – Cross connection campus resurvey (2 of 2), 1978; TD 1687 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - Annual physical facilities report, 1980; TD 1715 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - Subsurface investigation boiler house and fuel storage tanks, 1981; TD 1764 (Box-folder 14-3)
  - McConnell Hall remodel. Revised Building program, 1975; TD 1765 (Box-folder 14-4)
  - Utility Photos. Wildcat Shop Remodel, TD 1772 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - Photos. Electrical Utilities, TD 1773 (Box-folder 14-6)
  - Chestnut Mall Construction Photos, 1981; TD 1775 (Box-folder 14-7)
  - North Campus Landscaping and Lighting Construction Photos, TD 1776 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - Budget estimate for Bouillon Hall alterations, 1977; TD 1782 (Box-folder 14-9)
  - Bouillon library remodeling, 1970; TD 1784 (Box-folder 14-10)
  - Botany greenhouse, 1976; TD 1785 (Box-folder 14-11)
  - Student Village Instructional Facility, 1982; TD 1786 (Box-folder 14-12)
  - Boiler stack gas monitoring study, 1973; TD 1787 (Box-folder 14-13)
  - Cathodic Protection Systems, 1971; TD 1789 (Box-folder 14-14)
  - Corrosion Control Survey. Buried Utilities, 1973; TD 1790 (Box-folder 14-15)
  - Report of Soil Engineering Services, 1973; TD 1792 (Box-folder 14-16)
  - Soils and foundation investigation brooklane village, 1970; TD 1793 (Box-folder 14-17)
  - Foundation Investigation. Library Instructional Complex, 1971; TD 1794 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - McConnell Hall remodel. Revised Building program, 1975; TD 1795 (Box-folder 15-2)
  - S.U.B. Fire damage, 1982; TD 1796 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - Edison Hall, 1974; TD 1797 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - Design concept and criteria, Black Hall, 1959; TD 1798 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - Furnishings lists and estimates, 1971; TD 1799 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - Library instructional complex, 1968; TD 1800 (Box-folder 15-7)
  - Library Instructional Complex, Schematic Design I, 1968; TD 1801 (Box-folder 15-8)
  - Library Instructional Complex, Schematic Design II, 1968; TD 1802 (Box-folder 15-9)
  - Library Instructional; Complex, Design Development Drawings, 1970; TD 1803 (Box-folder 15-10)
  - Library Instructional Complex, Design Data, 1971; TD 1804 (Box-folder 15-11)
  - Study of alternative basement proposals. Library instructional complex, 1970; TD 1805 (Box-folder 15-12)
  - Construction Comparison Study for Brooklane Village, 1969; TD 1806 (Box-folder 15-13)
  - Building analysis. Administration Building, 1965; TD 1809 (Box-folder 15-14)
  - Fine and Applied Arts. Developmental Design and Outline Spec., 1967; TD 1807 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - Fine and Applied Arts Complex Photos, TD 1811 (Box-folder 16-2)